OldContractNo OldDisplayContractNo ContDate StrDate EndDate OldPropertyId OldPropertyNo OldUnitId OldUnitNo OldRenterId RenterName Account_Code OldAccountId TargetAccountId MissingProperty MissingUnit MissingRenter MissingOrUnmappedAccount InstallmentRows InstallmentTotal TruePaid TrueRemain SuggestedDecision
------------- -------------------- -------- ------- ------- ------------- ------------- --------- --------- ----------- ---------- ------------ ------------ --------------- --------------- ----------- ------------- ------------------------ --------------- ---------------- -------- ---------- -----------------
331.0 219030003 NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL 1 1 1 1 NULL NULL NULL NULL Contract shell row: core fields are blank. Exclude From Pilot / Archive Only.
689.0 120030012 NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL 1 1 1 1 NULL NULL NULL NULL Contract shell row: core fields are blank. Exclude From Pilot / Archive Only.
690.0 120030012 NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL 1 1 1 1 NULL NULL NULL NULL Contract shell row: core fields are blank. Exclude From Pilot / Archive Only.
721.0 219050021 NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL 1 1 1 1 NULL NULL NULL NULL Contract shell row: core fields are blank. Exclude From Pilot / Archive Only.
805.0 121080003 NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL 1 1 1 1 NULL NULL NULL NULL Contract shell row: core fields are blank. Exclude From Pilot / Archive Only.
945.0 119020012 NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL 1 1 1 1 NULL NULL NULL NULL Contract shell row: core fields are blank. Exclude From Pilot / Archive Only.
946.0 121070003 NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL 1 1 1 1 NULL NULL NULL NULL Contract shell row: core fields are blank. Exclude From Pilot / Archive Only.
947.0 121070003 NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL 1 1 1 1 NULL NULL NULL NULL Contract shell row: core fields are blank. Exclude From Pilot / Archive Only.
1626.0 119060033 NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL 1 1 1 1 NULL NULL NULL NULL Contract shell row: core fields are blank. Exclude From Pilot / Archive Only.
1716.0 119080012 NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL NULL 1 1 1 1 NULL NULL NULL NULL Contract shell row: core fields are blank. Exclude From Pilot / Archive Only.

(10 rows affected)
NoteSerial1 ContractRows
----------- ------------
119020012 5
119060033 9
119080012 9
120030012 9
121070003 8
121080003 3
219030003 6
219050021 4

(8 rows affected)
